qsrmagazine.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy Statement - QSR magazine

This web site is copyright 2014 **Journalistic Inc.  All Rights Reserved**

Effective Date: 12/15/2014

Our postal address is:   
101 Europa Drive, Suite 150  
Chapel Hill, NC 27517 

We can be reached via e-mail at [privacy@foodnewsmedia.com](mailto:privacy@foodnewsmedia.com) or you can reach us by telephone at (919) 945-0700, extension 120.  
  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Privacy Policy Administrator at 1-800-662-4834 ext 120 or [privacy@foodnewsmedia.com](mailto:privacy@foodnewsmedia.com).

**Information Collection and Used**

When you complete any form on one of our web sites, such as a Subscription Form, registration for a Webcast seminar, submit a request for information, and other forms, we are collecting personally identifiable information such as name, email address, address, and telephone number.  We use this information to provide you with your request and sometimes to collect data about our usage or readership or about industry to disseminate in aggregate and without reference to personally identifiable information. If you view content labeled as "Sponsored," we can sometimes identify you, and we may make the sponsor aware of your identity.  
  
Orders-  
If you apply for or purchase a subscription from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for fulfillment purposes. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.  
  
Third Party Subscription Requests-  
You have the option to provide the information of co-workers with whom you would like a subscription(s) to be sent (Name, email address, title). We will then send your co-worker the first issue of their subscription(s.). They will then have the option to choose to continue to receive the subscription(s). If this third party no longer would like to receive the subscription(s) they should follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each email or go to the subscriber information pages on the website.  
  
**Opting Out**  
  
Users have the option to request that their personal information be excluded from future communications, emails, or any other use, by requesting to be opted-out of such programs. [See the “Choice/Opt-Out” section.]  
  
**Log Files**  
  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data.  
  
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  
  
We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.  
  
**Cookies**  
  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.   
  
We use session ID cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site and hold items in your shopping cart, to improve our services. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser.   
  
We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. We may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information to monitor the usage of our site for marketing and design needs, as well as to maintain security against malicious activity.   
  
If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.   
  
Some of our advertisers use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers.”   
  
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [www.qsrmagazine.com](http://www.qsrmagazine.com/) or [www.fsrmagazine.com](http://www.fsrmagazine.com/) only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. [See the “Third Party Advertisers” section.] This statement also does not cover the use of cookies by other third party services, such as Facebook, Twitter, and Disqus.  
  
**Third Party Advertisers**  
  
Third Party Ad Servers-  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by third party ad servers. We share Web site usage information about users with reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site.

In addition, we have implemented the Google Display Advertising Feature on our web site.  This feature allows us to place a cookie on your computer to aid in recognizing you as a user of our web site.  As a user, the ads you might see in other places on the Internet have relevance to the kinds of content we provide on our web site.  This aids in making your ad experience more relevant.  You may opt out of this feature by visiting Google Analytics Display Advertiser Features you use, including through [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads), Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the [NAI's consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)).  You may also opt-out by using the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on found at [this link](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Ads on our web sites are delivered by Google to try and bring you offers that are of interest to you.  We have relationships with other companies, including Google, that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information. For further information, consult Google’s Privacy Policy at: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>. 

**Surveys, Contests, or Events**  
  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests or other events on our site. If you participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys, contests, or events is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, email address, and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).   
  
We use this information fulfill delivery of contest winnings, or contact you about delivery of these winnings or other needs. During the contest registration process you may be asked to opt-in or opt-out to receive information from survey, contest, or event sponsors. If you opt-in to receive this information, these reputable sponsors will be provided your contact information.   
  
Any additional information is used to study demographics, effectiveness, and other marketing research relevant to surveys, contests, or events.  
  
**Links to Other Sites**  
  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Journalistic, Inc. Please be aware that we, Journalistic, Inc. and QSR and FSR magazines, and Food News Media, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.   
  
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.   
  
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.   
  
**Choice/Opt-out**  
  
We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.   
  
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [eletters@foodnewsmedia.com](mailto:eletters@foodnewsmedia.com). We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our subscriber information pages, or you may contact us at 1-800-662-4834, ext 120, [privacy@foodnewsmedia.com](mailto:privacy@foodnewsmedia.com), or 101 Europa Drive, Suite 150, Chapel Hill, NC 27517 to opt out.  

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.   
  
Based upon our opt-in policy, we may send you information from third-parties who have paid us to distribute literature to those who might be interested.  With each emailing, you have the option of opting out of future emailings.  We do not release any of your contact information to third parties except under these circumstances:  1) You have requested specific information from a company; 2) you are participating in a Webinar program; in this case, we provide your information to the program sponsors; 3) you download a white paper provided by a specific company.  In each of these circumstances, we provide your information based on your request and use of these products.  If you do not want your information provided in this way, please do not use these particular products.

If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations after you have opted to receive them, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address or by writing to us at the above mailing address.  
  
**Communications From The Site**  
  
Special Offers and Updates-  
We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page.   
  
Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”   
  
Newsletters-  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.   
  
Service-related Announcements-  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.   
  
Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You may opt-out of these communications. Please see “Choice and Opt-out.”   
  
**Customer Service**  
  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you your subscription information via email. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.  
  
**Service Providers**  
  
We use other third parties to provide Webcast seminars and reprint ordering services on our site. When you sign up for Webcast seminars or reprint services, we will share your basic contact information and request as necessary, solely for the third party to provide that service.   
  
These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing.   
  
**Legal Disclaimer**  
  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.  
  
**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them.   
  
Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.

**Credit Card Data**

If you purchase a product or service on our site and use a credit card, please be advised that this information is accepted on third party sites which offer high level secure transactions.  Journalistic, Inc. has no control over the security of this data.  Journalistic, Inc. does not collect or store credit card data and has no access to this information when it is provided.  Charges are processed by third parties and only the funds and basic payment information are transmitted to us in order to complete the transaction Your credit card number, CVV and expiration date are never part of the information that is transmitted.

**Security**  
  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [privacy@foodnewsmedia.com](mailto:privacy@foodnewsmedia.com).  
  
**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.   
  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.   
  
**Contact Us**  
  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 1-800-662-4834, ext 120, [privacy@foodnewsmedia.com](mailto:privacy@foodnewsmedia.com), 101 Europa Drive, Suite 150, Chapel Hill, NC 27517.
